Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
- Are they here?
- Yes.
Meet HAN's CEO, Ms. Han Jeong-yeon.
It's a pleasure.
Welcome to Appello.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kang Ha-gi.
Thank you for coming here in person.
It must've been a long trip.
Let's go inside.
Allow me to escort you.
This way, please.
Watch out for the steps.
- Please.
- I'm fine.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
She's gorgeous.
The proposal I received from Appello
was impressive.
So I wanted to come here myself.
HAN has selected
SE: ON and Appello
as our preferred bidders
and would like to give you
the same assignment.
Sorry?
It's simple.
Who are HAN's customers?
Let's define that.
Are you asking us
to conduct customer profiling?
You're right.
We'll select our partner based
on the pitches from both companies.
Goodness.
This won't be easy.
It's tricky.
EPISODE 10
How am I supposed
to make sense of this situation?
I recently ran into her by chance.
She wanted a tour of Appello,
so I welcomed her
and she stabs my back like this.
It's just business.
Chan only found out today
that I was HAN's CEO.
Anyway.
It's great to get together again.
The three of us.
Then the CEOs should chat.
I have to be somewhere.
I can't believe the CEO came
instead of sending the managers.
That's cool.
Didn't something seem kind of odd?
What? How?
- It was Mr. Kang's face.
- Yes?
It seemed like they were
acquainted.
Who's the director in charge
of this store?
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kang Ha-gi.
Who is this?
She's the woman from the photo.
You haven't changed
both in your departure...
and return.
Let's eat dinner.
I've got plans.
I'm asking as HAN's CEO.
I have something important to say.
I'm sorry, Da-reum.
My meeting with Ms. Han
is taking longer than I thought.
I'm sorry.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
It's all right.
It's important for our company,
so it should be your priority.
I understand.
What is this?
I was excited to meet
Namda's first-ever boyfriend.
It's a bit much
to bail on us at the last minute.
This meeting is really important.
Please let him off.
- Wait, Ha-gi isn't coming today?
- My gosh.
Hello.
What's going on?
I wanted to sneak in
and introduce myself too.
Why would you do that?
You're Da-reum's friend.
I'm Ha-gi's friend.
Da-reum and Ha-gi are a couple.
Mi-mi and I are practically...
Instructor and student, right?
Well, allow me to treat you
in Ha-gi's place today.
- What would you like?
- What?
Let's order. What do you want?
- I'm okay.
- Excuse me!
My gosh.
What should we order?
- Can we order a lot?
- Yes, as much as you want.
I thought you'd be glad to see me.
You aren't exactly a fond memory,
so not really.
I found out much later.
MAKER SPACE WORKSHOP
- No, not really for me.
- Really?
- Then do you have to do it?
- Maybe later.
Chan!
The reason
Chan became a trainee and left
was because of us.
That day
I had lost my closest friend.
Of course, he's back in my life.
But we still don't talk about that.
Then you left to study abroad
without a word
so I was left alone.
How is that a great memory?
You're right.
I should've told you before I left.
Was it tough for you?
We weren't that serious.
We only dated for a few months.
From time to time
whenever I thought of Korea
I thought of you.
What's this important thing
you wanted to tell me as HAN's CEO?
Wait, who?
Han Jeong-yeon?
From school?
Oh, so they weren't classmates,
but she was a senior.
Yes, a year older.
This is getting interesting.
I mean, she's Ha-gi's first love.
Back then, she was
so popular with the guys.
Gosh, don't even get me started.
Chan was into her too.
She was pretty much
everyone's first love.
Gosh, this is fascinating.
How did they reunite?
- So she was his first love?
- Yes.
It was back in high school.
That's an ancient story.
She's still gorgeous, right?
My heart would race so quickly
if I ran into my first love.
- Let's just drink, shall we?
- Yes, cheers.
- Cheers!
HAN DIDN'T CREATE A BRAND
BUT AN AESTHETIC
SE: ON'S DEFINITION
OF HAN'S PHILOSOPHY
SE: ON and Appello's proposals
looked far too similar.
It's not a coincidence, is it?
There's a spy among us.
- I've been looking.
- I knew it.
Does anyone come to mind?
I'm not...
completely sure yet.
I thought you and I
might share the same goal.
I didn't meet with SE: ON
to sign with them.
I went to get revenge.
I'll get my revenge,
and you can find the spy.
Don't you think we could pull it off
if we worked together?
Think about it.
Jeez.
Hey, you're his current girlfriend.
And you're absolutely charming too.
Who cares about first love?
Darn it. She has nothing on you.
- She doesn't!
- She kind of does.
Darn you.
She's absolutely gorgeous.
Hey, student. Quiet.
Who is your boyfriend into right now?
- It's you.
- She's right! It's you!
You guys are right!
- Yes!
- It's Nam Da-reum.
- She's right.
Instructor and student.
It's me.
Just an instructor and a student.
Yes, it's me.
What?
I'm sorry. I'm late.
How did you get here?
I'll drink this
as punishment for being late.
As you should.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, my.
All right.
- That's cool.
- Lucky you.
We're going for round two, right?
What round two?
But we should.
Please excuse us.
I'll schedule something
more proper next time.
Hey, man.
Stop.
I'm watching you.
- Stop.
- If you ever make my Da-reum cry
you will cry tears of blood, man.
Got it?
Right. Yes.
We should go, Ms. Da-reum.
- Bye, girls.
- Bye.
See you soon.
- So, round two?
- What round two? Let's go home.
Hey, do you want to go for round two?
Mi-mi.
I really thought
we had something going on.
Min-woo.
Do you really like me?
I fell for you at first sight.
When I work, eat, shower
or even sit in the restroom,
you're all I think about.
The thought of you
never leaves my mind all day long.
Do you remember
my ideal type?
Your ideal type?
A competent guy who's a good kisser?
I hate bad kissers.
Did we kiss for real?
This is insane!
See you tomorrow, Mi-mi!
Yes!
I'm fine now.
Are you mad that I couldn't make it?
No.
I'm not that petty.
Then why are you pouting?
I heard you were close
to Ms. Han Jeong-yeon
back in high school.
Oh, yes. Right.
We were friends.
Is that all?
That's all.
Kim Min-woo, you punk.
Ms. Da-reum.
I heard Ms. Han was your first love.
- Well, it's...
- Was it nice to reunite with her?
That you even missed our dinner?
Don't take it the wrong way.
It's all in the past.
She proposed a project,
so the meeting took a while.
What is it?
It's very important for Appello.
It's a bit sensitive,
so I can't disclose everything.
But I wouldn't lie to you.
Can you give me a little more time?
Don't ever get anxious.
Because the one I like right now...
is you, Ms. Da-reum.
I know that.
Trust me, okay?
THE CAT I MET ON MY WALK
REMINDED ME OF YOU
IT WAS CHATTY AND CUTE
HAN JEONG-YEON
- Hey.
- I just met with Ha-gi.
What were you two talking about?
You know, old memories.
You told me to win his heart.
And?
It killed my pride.
He seemed unbothered
by his first love.
I might start trying harder.
What do you mean?
What's wrong?
Wasn't this what you wanted?
You don't have to feel so guilty.
Because
I want Ha-gi back
for myself again.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW HAN,
YOU DON'T KNOW FASHION
CLOTHES THAT STAY WITH YOU
"Clothes that stay with you."
You want to work
with a designated employee?
Yes, it's weird to reach out
to the CEO every single time.
Did you say it was Ms. Nam Da-reum
who wrote the proposal?
I want her.
- Why Ms. Da-reum of all people?
- I told you already.
I liked Appello's proposal.
I loved the level of understanding
she has of my brand.
I'll see if Ms. Da-reum
will be interested.
I can ask now.
Ms. Nam Da-reum?
- Yes.
- I loved your proposal.
I need someone who'll handle
my business with Appello.
Would you like to lead the project?
I'd be happy to,
if Mr. Kang is okay with it.
It's a great opportunity, I guess.
But it's your opinion that matters.
What do you think?
In that case
I want to do it.
Excellent. I look forward to it.
You don't have to feel so guilty.
Because
I want Ha-gi back for myself again.
WON-BIN
Hey, Won-bin.
I've got bad news, Chan.
You're here.
Let's go.
First, put these on.
No, I didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't leave behind
weird photos or videos, right?
What do you take me for?
Anyway, Jinu and Teo
were the ones who got hacked.
Why are you getting summoned? Gosh.
I'm nervous to death.
There it is.
INVESTIGATION DIVISION
Thankfully, the hacker was arrested
before any information got leaked.
The data he used to blackmail them
included unreleased songs and videos
related to you, Mr. Lee.
I wanted to check with you.
Wait.
These are materials you used
for your album preparations.
It was supposedly
for the five of you.
It must've been important.
They even gave the hacker money
and tried to stop it.
They tried that hard?
And they didn't even tell me.
Boys.
Chan.
You should've called me first
when this happened.
What money did you have
to hand over to that guy?
I mean, it included Chan's data...
and songs you worked on for years.
We disbanded a decade ago.
Why are you still like this?
Go live your life now. Please.
You may be done, but not us.
For us
D.N.X is everything.
Sorry.
We'll try not to stand in your way
from now on.
Hey, Jinu.
Jinu.
You must be working hard
for the presentation
so I prepared this meeting
to show you my support.
There's nothing much for us to do.
We've caught up with Appello
as soon as our platform launched.
We'll take first place in no time.
And we're almost done
with customer profiling.
HAN's customers must be those
who are drawn to scarcity.
The desire to have something
that you cannot have.
You're right. People line up
before the opening because of that.
Scarcity.
We should approach the Korean market
with the same
limited-edition strategy.
That's an interesting take.
What does
Appello think?
I can't say for sure.
We're still
working on it.
Goodness. We should eat.
It looks great.
Something's going on between
Kang Ha-gi and Han Jeong-yeon.
Find out what it is.
HERITY FACTORY:
MODERN POP-UP SHOWROOM
You're still here.
Hey, Director Lee.
I was passing by,
and I saw the lights on.
If anyone is working until now,
it had to be you.
I had to work on something.
Don't you go on dates?
I know, right?
Have you eaten?
I met
Jinu and Teo at the police station.
The police station?
They got hacked
and the data
was all about D.N.X's comeback.
They still haven't given up
on that dream.
I didn't know they were so desperate.
But you feel the same way.
Wasn't that why you had been
working on that fan song?
You're right.
But I guess I must have no courage.
The courage to throw away
great opportunities
and my career.
Is it because
that's the practical choice?
I should focus on my movie, right?
Whatever choice you make
I want you to do
what your heart tells you to do.
Something for yourself.
Whatever choice you make
I want you to do
what your heart tells you to do.
Something for yourself.
- All right!
- Come with me.
I'm over here.
Ms. Da-reum.
Look.
What is this?
It's so pretty. What is this?
My gosh. Did you prepare all this?
How pretty.
When did you look these up
and prepare everything?
Well, you know.
I just saw it by coincidence.
Is that true?
Try this.
- Do you like it?
- This is good too.
The weekend feels so short.
I don't want to go to work tomorrow.
How can you say that
in front of your CEO?
What?
I was talking to my boyfriend.
4 P.M. GO TO THE LAKE
5 P.M. WATCH THE REFLECTION
Do you want to move to the lake?
- Why?
- Because...
I heard it's beautiful at sunset.
To show me the light reflection?
But I just want to stay here.
1 P.M. LUNCH AT THE RESTAURANT
2 P.M. CAFE
3 P.M. PICNIC ON THE GRASS
4 P.M. GO TO THE LAKE
We don't have to move
according to your plan.
Why are you trying so hard
to impress me today?
I didn't get to meet
your friends properly last time.
And we haven't seen
each other lately.
Did that bother you?
I wanted to do it right this time.
It's because of Ms. Han, isn't it?
- I...
- You said I had nothing to worry.
I decided to take on HAN
because I trust you.
You don't have to try that hard.
I just like it when we're together.
Thank you.
Do you want to lie down again?
No, I want to stay like this.
Beyond the forgotten memories
I want to go up into the sky
Get on
Oh, gosh.
It's been so long
that I don't remember anything.
You're getting old.
Wait till you're my age.
It's not easy to dance like this.
Anyway, it's so nice
to practice together.
- Me too.
- You're grossing me out. Get off me.
It would've been nice
if Chan was here.
Don't get your hopes up.
D.N.X means nothing
to a top star like him.
He's on his way to Hollywood.
Why don't we try it again?
Let's start from "Get on."
MYEONGMYEONG BUILDING
MYU DANCE STUDIO
Roy.
I don't care who you like.
But
it's too much for us
to handle right now.
Let's keep it a secret.
Later...
When things get better...
Just until then.
Okay.
SHOCKING PICTURES OF ROY
AND HIS BOYFRIEND
DARK CLOUDS OVER D.N.X,
ALL EYES ON THEIR FUTURE
Stop reading it.
- Chan, what do we do now?
- That's why I told you...
You should've been more careful, Roy.
Roy!
- Hey.
- Don't do this to Roy.
- Stop.
- Move. Get out of my way!
- Don't do this too.
- I said, move!
You're no different.
The two of you ruined
everything we built!
QUICK DELIVERY
- Hi, I'm back.
- Good job today.
Hey, the boss saw him.
He really is a celebrity.
He was a member of some group
called D.N. something.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- But it's true. I swear.
- Want to bet 50,000 won?
- You called it.
- Yes.
- Deal.
You said 50,000 won.
Hey, take off your helmet
for a second.
We've worked together for months,
but I still haven't seen your face.
Hey, I heard you were an idol.
- Is it true? Show me.
- No.
- Hey, take it off.
- Take it off, will you?
- Why won't you take it off?
- Let me see your face.
Seriously, don't you have
anything else to do?
What on earth are you doing
when you should be
working hard at this busy hour?
Who are you?
Triple the delivery fee.
There's a limited time event.
TRIPLE THE DELIVERY FEE
TIME EVENT
- It's true.
- I can't miss this.
I'll see you when I come back.
It's only on for two hours.
Stop bothering him.
Thank you.
Then can you make some time for me?
Thank you, Seul-a.
That's all you drink.
How did you know?
Because I was your fan.
No, it's not that I was.
I still am.
I started
this delivery job to find you.
- What?
- To see if it really was you.
Then I realized it was you.
Honestly, I don't care what you do.
But you never take the helmet off.
That really upsets me.
I know that you feel bad
about what happened to the team.
But I don't want you
to live as if you never existed
just because of that.
I've never been ashamed of you.
Back then or now.
So...
don't hide yourself,
at least from me.
I made a list of pop-up stores
that would fit HAN's concept.
I like the space.
The location is good.
Only global luxury brands have held
pop-up stores there.
There's intense competition
for the space, not just from us.
It must've required a lot of legwork.
Not at all.
However
the streets may be crowded
but none of them are my customers.
I beg your pardon?
Is this all you prepared?
PROJECT PROPOSAL
Wait.
Actually, aside from the places
you saw in the meeting
I have another one in mind.
Where are we?
This is Ikseon-dong.
I looked into why HAN's main branch
in Paris is
located in the old streets
of Saint-Germain
instead of Rue Saint-Honoré,
where all the luxury brands are.
It's a place with unique cafes,
private bookstores
and a lot of vintage shops.
It's where people
with a strong sense of style go.
I thought about where those people
would go in Korea.
And?
My impression is that HAN's customers
like to walk, explore, and stay.
They buy something
that reflects what they like.
I'm finally starting to like it.
Sure.
Let's keep looking around.
Yes, Ms. Han.
My first brand didn't work out.
Then is HAN your second one?
I started it with a friend
from fashion school
and we got good responses
when we first opened.
Then why didn't it work out?
My friend went behind my back
and I lost everything
to a major corporation.
I started from scratch again.
That led to HAN now.
It must've been tough.
It was, but that helped me grow up.
It taught me what I was capable of.
I realized I was relying
on her sense a lot
and not my own.
So when I started HAN,
I focused on myself
like what I could present
and what I was good at.
She's undeniably cool.
What about you, Ms. Da-reum?
Do you feel like the work you do
at Appello is truly yours?
I'm still learning.
I think I'm getting there.
By any chance
does my relationship
with Mr. Kang bother you?
I'd be lying if I said no.
That's very honest.
But I...
I trust the person I'm dating.
Do you?
In the end
HAN's customers must be those
who are drawn to scarcity.
Come on.
What are you so worried about?
Ms. Han Jeong-yeon seems kind to us.
You shouldn't worry so much.
Seong-wook.
SE's ideas are too similar to ours.
But it's normal for ideas like that
to overlap in this field.
Hey, don't you think
you're being too sensitive lately?
I wish that was the case.
Don't worry.
Come on.
There's nothing to worry about.
Okay?
Right.
Thank you for everything today.
I appreciate it.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
It's okay. I'm expecting someone.
- Bye now.
- Okay, I'll see you later.
I'm going to tell him
I pulled it off today.
The person you're trying to reach
is not available.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
ANNUAL PERFORMANCE REPORT
SE CORPORATION QUARTERLY PERFORMANCE
BY DIVISION
ILLEGAL SUBCONTRACT
INVESTIGATION REPORT
SE CORPORATION BUSINESS ANALYSIS
CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION LEAK
SE spent too much on marketing
after starting their platform.
It's like they were gambling.
How did you secure this?
Through the agency
that consulted SE: ON.
I've been tracking their movement
since before I came to Korea.
It's always the same for SE.
They call it
collaboration and investment
but all they're thinking about
is taking over other companies.
I know it from experience.
They approached us the same way.
MS. NAM DA-REUM:
WHERE ARE YOU?
I JUST FINISHED
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
I can't even call him.
I'm so pathetic.
CHAN
- Hi, Chan.
- What are you up to, Da-reum?
Nothing much.
Then do you want to listen to this?
Listen to what?
One second.
What do you think?
I love it.
It feels comforting.
I've been stuck,
but you helped me work through it.
I did?
I just went with my heart
like you said.
Go with my heart...
I should've done this earlier.
Thanks, Da-reum.
I said that...
when I couldn't even do it myself.
What's that?
Nothing.
Let me hear it when you're done.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Want a glass?
No, thanks.
When can I talk to you again
not as the CEO of Appello
but as Kang Ha-gi?
Next time.
With Chan too.
MISSED CALL
MS. NAM DA-REUM
By any chance
does my relationship
with Mr. Kang bother you?
But I...
I trust the person I'm dating.
Do you?
It's okay. I'm expecting someone.
Is it too late?
I missed you.
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
Yes.
I saw you
entering Ms. Han's hotel earlier.
Were you with her all this while?
- I...
- You didn't tell me.
And I couldn't reach you.
If I hadn't seen you, I wouldn't have
known you were together.
- It's a misunderstanding.
- If it's not, what is it?
Later.
I'll tell you later.
I'm sorry.
But I'm...
I'm your girlfriend.
How am I different from a stranger?
Ms. Da-reum...
I'm sorry.
I can't pretend to be okay right now.
- It's the final presentation data.
- Okay.
CUSTOMER PROFILING REPORT
APPELLO
But Mr. Kang
this is completely different from
what we discussed in the meeting.
Why did it change?
I leaked that on purpose.
This is the real data.
We have to be careful
until the presentation.
Please go over it.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
They must've had a fight, right?
Isn't this the first time
since they started dating?
It's so obvious. It's suffocating me.
I can feel it.
What now?
Maybe they're faking it,
so they won't get caught.
What?
But it's true.
I'm very sharp, you know?
Da-reum.
- There you are.
- Are you here to see me?
Yes, you said you wanted to hear
the fan song when it was ready.
Oh, right.
You didn't sound well last time
I talked to you on the phone.
I was also worried if you were okay.
I'm fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
Should we listen to it
in the showroom? There are speakers.
Sure.
- Can you put it on bluetooth?
- Yes.
SETTINGS
I don't think she's caught on
to what we've been up to yet.
I'm going to tell her the truth.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
- It's the same, down to every word.
- This is crazy.
How can it be the same?
Mr. Kang didn't come to work today.
He never once missed work
rain or shine,
or even when he was sick.
I'll stay by your side to the end.
There's something I want to do.
We never waited for you.
I didn't want to hide it anymore.
I LOVE LEE CHAN
I wanted to show you
that this is who I am,
and the part of me that loves you
is also a part of who I am.
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs